#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/dhananjana (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

.NET Framework

C#

#### **Certifications**

Machine Learning

Google Cloud Platform
Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure

AWS Fundamentals: Going Cloud-

Native

AWS Fundamentals: Building Serverless Applications

**AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner** 

# Sachintha Dhananjana

Senior Software Engineer at Calcey

Gampaha District, Western Province, Sri Lanka

### Summary

Graduated from the University of Moratuwa with specialized in Computer Science and Engineering. I like to explore more knowledge and experience in the software engineering field. I am always open to learning new languages and technologies as well as building my career in the IT sector

#### Experience

Calcey

1 year 3 months

Senior Software Engineer January 2023 - Present (9 months)

Software Engineer
July 2022 - January 2023 (7 months)
Colombo, Western Province, Sri Lanka

Stack Technologies
Software Engineer
January 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 7 months)

Moraspirit Initiative Web Developer March 2018 - January 2021 (2 years 11 months) Sri Lanka

Stack Technologies Software Developer March 2020 - October 2020 (8 months) Sri Lanka

ProavosLabs
Software Engineer Intern
July 2019 - December 2019 (6 months)

Sri Lanka

Avtra

Software Engineer Intern July 2019 - December 2019 (6 months)

Sri Lanka

Based at Avtra's development centre - Proavos Labs

## Education

University of Moratuwa

· (2016 - 2020)

University of Moratuwa

Bachelor of Science - BSc, Computer Science and Engineering · (2016 - 2020)